[
    {
        "title" : "Monarchy"
    },


    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Name first 10 in line of succession to the British throne",
      "answer": "William The Prince of Wales"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Name first 10 in line of succession to the British throne",
        "answer": "Prince George of Wales"
    },

    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Name first 10 in line of succession to the British throne",
        "answer": "Princess Charlotte of Wales"
      },
      {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "Name first 10 in line of succession to the British throne",
          "answer": "Prince Louis of Wales"
      },

    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Name first 10 in line of succession to the British throne",
        "answer": "Harry The Duke of Sussex"
      },
      {
          "id": 6,
          "question": "Name first 10 in line of succession to the British throne",
          "answer": "Prince Archie of Sussex"
      },

    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Name first 10 in line of succession to the British throne",
        "answer": "Princess Lilibet of Sussex"
      },
      {
          "id": 8,
          "question": "Name first 10 in line of succession to the British throne",
          "answer": "Andrew The Duke of York"
      },

    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Name first 10 in line of succession to the British throne",
        "answer": "Princess Beatrice, Mrs. Edoardo Mapelli Mozzi"
      },
      {
          "id": 10,
          "question": "Name first 10 in line of succession to the British throne",
          "answer": "Miss Sienna Mapelli Mozzi"
      }
]
  